Whip Networks Services - Privacy Policy \[UPDATED\]
===================================================

Updated and Effective Date: This privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy”) is effective and was last updated as of April 22, 2024.

This Privacy Policy applies to tvtime.com, the TV Time mobile application, and any other TV Time branded website, mobile application, or other feature or service offered by Whip Networks, Inc. (“WNI”) that posts this Privacy Policy (collectively, “TV Time”). This Privacy Policy describes our practices with regard to the data we collect through TV Time and your choices.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing or using TV Time, you agree to this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Service.](https://www.tvtime.com/terms)

Table of Contents
-----------------

1. [Information We Collect and How We Collect It](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_1)
2. [How We Use Your Information](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_2)
3. [How We Share Your Information](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_3)
4. [Third Party Advertising and Analytics](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_4)
5. [Third Party Content and Links](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_5)
6. [Your Choices About the Information We Collect](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_6)
7. [Security of Your Information](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_7)
8. [General Audience Services](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_8)
9. [Changes to This Privacy Policy](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_9)
10. [Consent to International Transfer of Your Information](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_10)
11. [How Long We Retain Your Information](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_11)
12. [Contact Us](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_12)
13. [Notice to Nevada Residents](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_13)
14. [Notice to California Residents \[UPDATED\]](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_14)
15. [Information for European Union/European Economic Area and UK Residents](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_15)
16. [Additional Information for Canadian Residents](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_16)
17. [Additional Information if You Are Located in Countries Outside the US, EU/EEA, UK, or Canada](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_17)

### 1\. Information We Collect and How We Collect It

We may collect information from you both directly and automatically when you use TV Time. Some of this information may be considered “personal information” under various applicable laws. We consider information that identifies you as a specific, identified individual to be personal information (such as your name and email address), and we treat additional information, including IP addresses and cookie identifiers, as “personal information” where required by applicable law. Note that we may de-identify personal information so that it is non-personal, such as by aggregating it or converting it to a code, sometimes using a function commonly known as a “hash.” We maintain and use de-identified data without attempting to re-identify it, except where permitted by applicable law, such as to determine whether our de-identification process satisfies legal requirements. We will treat de-identified information as non-personal to the fullest extent allowed by applicable law.

We collect information in the following ways:

* **Information You Submit Via TV Time**. In the course of using TV Time, you may provide us with certain information, including contact information (such as your name, email address, and social media username); information about your interests and preferences (such as your favorites and the episodes that you have watched); account information (such as your profile picture, username, and birthday); and demographic information (such as your gender and the country you are from). Some features may allow you to view, create, reproduce, submit, display, perform, and/or share content, which includes videos, audio, images, graphics, written posts, comments, and other forms of multimedia (collectively, “User Content”).
    
* **Information We Collect Automatically From Your Use of TV Time**. When you use TV Time, we, our third-party service providers, and our business partners may automatically collect certain information (“Usage Information”). One of the ways we collect Usage information is when you visit portions of TV Time, our servers automatically generate logs to help us determine how people travel through TV Time and to improve our services. Usage Information is generally non-identifying, but if we associate it with you as a specific and identifiable person, we treat it as personal information. This Usage Information includes your IP address and unique device identifiers (“Device IDs”) for your computer, mobile phone, or other device used to access TV Time. A Device ID is a number that is automatically assigned to your device, and our servers identify your device by its Device ID. We will also collect and track other data and information relating to your device, including entertainment-specific and/or streaming applications on your device, the Internet service provider you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the type of browser you use. We track your activities on TV Time such as the pages and content you access and your interactions with the content we provide. We may be able to infer your approximate location based on your IP address or similar information we collect.

We use the following types of tracking technologies (collectively referred to as “Tracking Technologies”) to automatically collect information when you interact with us online:

* **Cookies and Local Storage** are small text files stored locally on your device that help store user preferences. These technologies are able to store a unique identifier for a device to us to recognize the device whenever the device is used to visit TV Time. These technologies may be used for many purposes by us, our service providers, and our third-party business partners, such as automatically collecting Usage Information, enabling features, serving advertisements to you online, and remembering your preferences. We may use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on TV Time, to study the effectiveness of our customer communications, to manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on or delivered by or through TV Time, and to personalize your experience through TV Time, such as to recognize you when you return to TV Time. The information we store includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. If you do not want to accept cookies, you can block them by adjusting the settings on your Internet browser. You can find more information about cookies and how they work at [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/).
    
* **Web beacons (also known as clear GIFs and pixel tags)** are small pieces of code used to collect usage analytics. They help us to determine, for instance, whether a page has been viewed or not and, if so, how many times. When you ask us to send you information on a promotion or a newsletter, we will use web beacons to establish how many of the emails are actually opened.
    
    We use similar tools to collect such information from mobile devices. In addition, we may use a variety of other technologies that collect similar information for security and fraud detection purposes.
    
* **Information from Third Parties**. We may receive information about you from third parties, such as data providers who enhance the information we have about you, publicly available information, or third parties that you integrate into TV Time, such as social media platforms or streaming services.
    
* **Social Media and Other Third Party Platforms**. We may permit you to interact with social media and other third party platforms, including Google, Apple, Netflix, Facebook, and Twitter. When you interact with third party platforms through TV Time, we will receive information about you. We may also receive information about you if other users of social media give us access to their profiles and you are one of their connections or "friends." The information we collect is subject to this Privacy Policy. The information collected and stored by the third party remains subject to the third party’s privacy practices, including, without limitation, whether the third party continues to share information with us, the types of information shared, and your choices with regard to what is visible to others on that third-party website or service. We or the third party may allow you to disable or remove the application or feature, in which case we will no longer collect information about you through the application or feature, but we may retain the information previously collected.
    
    If you choose to post information to a third party platform, that information may be public and the third party may have access to information about you and your use of TV Time. You may also choose to participate in a way that connects that third-party service with TV Time, such as posting to one of our pages on a social media site or sharing your watch history from a streaming service with us. Doing so may allow us to collect (or the third party to share) information about you, including personal information, and the third party may allow us to re-post content related to us on our own services.
    
    In addition, these third parties may set their own cookies and collect information about your use of TV Time, including your IP address or other device identifiers, and which pages you visit on TV Time. Certain third-party platforms may be able to collect certain information on your visits to TV Time regardless of whether or not you affirmatively interact with the feature and whether or not you are logged into (or have) an account. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of third parties that control platforms you post to or that connect to TV Time and set your privacy preferences with them.

### 2\. How We Use Your Information

We may use non-personal information for any purpose, including for advertising, research, and marketing purposes. We also use information that we collect, including personal information and Usage Information, as disclosed in this Privacy Policy and as follows:

* to provide TV Time to you and allow you to participate in the features TV Time offers, including to register your account, and to participate in community forums such as comments and reviews, and to administer and manage referral marketing programs;
* to customize and optimize our content for you based on the streaming apps you may have, such as recommendations, promotions, and advertisements we display to you both when you use TV Time and elsewhere online;
* to provide information on products or services we think you may be interested in, including special offers and promotions from us, our advertisers, and third-party partners, using the contact information you provide;
* to improve and monetize TV Time, which may include tracking traffic, usage, trends and navigation patterns related to your activities on TV Time and appending third-party aggregated data to your information;
* to create aggregated and anonymized surveys, reports, and other analytics based on your use of TV Time which we may share with content providers, advertisers, television production companies, cable networks, OTT platforms, talent agencies or others in the television industry, indicating what viewers thought of certain shows, and what activity there was on TV Time after viewing them;
* to contact you to respond to your questions, feedback, or requests or to provide you with technical support;
* to communicate with you about the services, content, features or products you use or request, including to provide you with information concerning changes to TV Time which may affect your account and/or your use of TV Time, or in our discretion, changes to our policies;
* to respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
* for internal business purposes, including to prevent fraud or other illegal activity, to prevent imminent bodily harm, or to protect ourselves and you from people violating our Terms of Service, or otherwise to protect our or third-party rights or interests, which may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, courts, or other government entities; and
* in any other way we describe when you provide the information, or otherwise with your prior consent.

### 3\. How We Share Your Information

We may aggregate, de-identify, and/or anonymize any information collected through TV Time such that such information is no longer linked to your personal information. We may share non-personal information (including hashed or other de-identified data) with third parties for advertising and other purposes. We do not share your personal information with third parties for those third parties’ own direct marketing purposes unless we provide you the opportunity to opt-in or opt-out prior to such sharing, as required by applicable law.

In addition, we may share the information we have collected about you, including personal information and Usage Information, as disclosed at the time you provide us with information or your consent, and as described in this Privacy Policy, including:

* **Publicly Posted Content/At Your Request.**Portions of your User Content and profile information may be available to registered users of and other visitors to TV Time, who may also be able to share it outside TV Time. We may also share information when you direct us to do so, such as if you choose to link your account with a social networking service or other third party application or feature through which information is shared, or if we present you with an opportunity to receive marketing offers from a third party. We do not control the actions of third parties and you post content and share your information at your own risk.
    
* **Service Providers.** We contract with certain companies to perform services on our behalf, including advertising, marketing assistance, e-mail delivery, hosting services, site maintenance and repair, security, quality assurance, customer service, surveys, trailers, and data research and analysis, and provide your information to them only to fulfill such services.
    
* **Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions.** We may offer sweepstakes, contests, or other promotions (any of which, a “Promotion”) that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to the provisions, conditions, or official rules that govern the Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you (including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the Promotion to use your name, voice, likeness, or other indicia of persona in advertising or marketing materials). If you choose to enter a Promotion, personal information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, as required by law, or as permitted by the Promotion’s terms or official rules (such as on a winner’s list).
    
* **Affiliated Entities Within Whip Networks, Inc. for Their Business Purposes.**We offer a number of websites and services to consumers and businesses, and we may share information among our affiliated corporate entities for their business purposes. You may request further details about the current list of entities that have this information – see the “[Contact Us](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_13)” section below.
    
* **In Connection with Business Transactions**. In the event WNI undergoes a business transition, such as a merger with or acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, we may transfer your personal information and other information to the successor organization in connection with such transaction, including during the course of any due diligence. By providing your personal information, you agree that we may transfer such information to the other entity in such a transaction without your further consent. If material changes to TV Time’s privacy practices will occur as a result of the business transition, WNI or its successor will attempt to notify you, including by posting a notice on TV Time so that you can elect whether to delete your Account.
    
* **For Administrative and Legal Reasons.** We reserve the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation, or legal request; to protect the integrity of TV Time; to fulfill your requests; to cooperate in a law enforcement investigation, an investigation on a public safety matter, or an investigation into claims of intellectual property infringement; to protect and defend the legal rights and/or property of WNI and any of our subsidiaries, affiliates, and shareholders, or TV Time, it any of their users, or any other party; or, in an emergency, to protect the health and safety of users or the general public.

### 4\. Third Party Advertising and Analytics

WNI works with third party business partners such as online advertising companies, analytics providers, and other partners to serve our ads online, to serve third party ads through TV Time and to provide us with information regarding the use of TV Time and the effectiveness of our advertisements. We allow these companies to place tracking technologies like cookies and web tags on TV Time, and they may otherwise collect or have access to Usage Information and other information about you. Some of these parties may collect personal information over time when you visit TV Time or other online websites and services. We may share information, typically information that has been aggregated or de-identified, Usage Information, and location information with third party advertising companies, analytics providers, and other third parties including for targeted advertising purposes.

We use Google Analytics, which uses cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze information about the use of TV Time and report on activities and trends. This service may also collect information about the use of other websites, apps, and online services. You can learn about Google’s practices by going to [https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites), and opt out of them by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

We use a variety of third parties to perform advertising and analytics services, and some of these companies may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) or the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”). You may wish to visit[optout.networkadvertising.org](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1), which provides information regarding targeted advertising and the opt-out procedures of NAI members, including opt out mechanisms for web browsers, mobile and other connected devices, and a tool to opt out from participating NAI members using your hashed email address for interest-based advertising. You may also want to visit [optout.aboutads.info](https://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN), which provides information regarding targeted advertising and offers an opt-out for DAA-participating companies. If you are a California resident, please see our “[Notice to California Residents](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_14)” section below regarding additional rights you have, including how to exercise your “Do Not Sell” right.

**Options for the TV Time App**. Mobile devices may contain settings that allow you to disable tracking advertising and/or analytics. In addition, the digital advertising industry has provided the ability for mobile users to register their intent not to receive targeted advertising at [https://www.aboutads.info/appchoices](https://www.aboutads.info/appchoices).

Please note that opting out through these mechanisms does not opt you out of being served advertising, and that you will continue to receive generic ads while online.

If you are a California resident, please see our [NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS](https://tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_14) regarding additional rights you have, including how to exercise your “Do Not Sell” right.

### 5\. Third Party Content and Links

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including, but not limited to, any third party websites, services and applications (and the information or content contained therein) ("Third Party Services") that may be linked to or from TV Time and/or that you elect to access through TV Time. When you navigate away from TV Time to another site, this Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Those Third Party Services may use their own cookies or other tracking technologies, may independently collect information from you or about you, and match your data with data from other sources and use your data in ways other than described in this Privacy Policy. Your browsing and interaction on any Third Party Services is subject to such Third Party Services’ own rules and policies, which we encourage you to review prior to providing them with your information.

### 6\. Your Choices About the Information We Collect

We may provide you with the option to update some of your information, to make some of your information non-shareable with other users of TV Time, or to opt out of marketing communications through the profile or other settings areas of your account. In addition, you may opt out of marketing communications as set forth below.

* **Email.** You may unsubscribe from any marketing email we may send you through the opt-out mechanism included in each such email, or you can communicate your preferences to us by emailing us at [support@tvtime.com](mailto:support@tvtime.com). We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to your use of TV Time, service announcements, notices of changes to this Privacy Policy, or other terms, or similar administrative or transactional messages, and such messages will be unaffected by any choice to opt out of marketing communications.
    
* **Push Notifications**. With your consent, we may send promotional and non-promotional push notifications or alerts to your mobile device. You can elect to stop receiving those messages by changing the notification settings on your mobile device.
    
* **Other Privacy Rights.** If you are a resident of specific states or countries, you may have additional rights. Residents of the below listed regions should refer to the linked notices for more information on additional rights and how to exercise them:
    
    * [Information for European Union, European Economic Area, and United Kingdom Residents](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_15)
    * [Additional Information if You Are Located in Countries Outside the US, EU/EEA, UK, or Canada](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_17)

### 7\. Security of Your Information

We implement commercially reasonable security measures to protect the security of your information. However, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. We urge you to take steps to keep your personal information (including your account password) safe and to log out of your account after use.

### 8\. General Audience Services

The Services are not intended for users younger than the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from users younger than the age of 16.

### 9\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

To the extent allowed by applicable law, we reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. We will inform you by posting a notice on TV Time. We may also provide notice to you in other ways, such as through contact information you have provided. Your continued use of TV Time after the effective date of the revised Privacy Policy will constitute your consent to those changes to the fullest extent allowed by applicable law. However, we will provide notice and obtain your consent (opt-in or opt-out) if required. Note that you may no longer be able to use certain or any features of TV Time if you do not consent to the revised Privacy Policy.

### 10\. Consent to International Transfer of Your Information

We are a US-based company so if you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that the information that we collect from you will be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside of your country. By using TV Time or providing us with any information, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to this transfer to, and processing, usage, sharing, and storage of your information in the United States and other jurisdictions, which may have different or less protective privacy laws than those in your country. As a result, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States and other countries according to the laws in those jurisdictions. Your information will also be disclosed to third parties as described in the “How We Share Your Information” section above.

### 11\. How Long We Retain Your Information

We will retain your information for so long as needed to provide the TV Time services to you, or as required to fulfill our legal requirements and defend legal claims. After you have terminated your use of TV Time, we will store your information in an aggregated and anonymized format.

### 12\. Contact Us

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy and/or practices, please send an email to: [support@tvtime.com](mailto:support@tvtime.com). You may also contact us at Whip Networks, Inc., 1841 Centinela Ave., Santa Monica, CA 90404.

### 13\. Notice to Nevada Residents

Nevada S.B. 220 provides consumers with the ability to opt out of the sale of their personal information. We do not sell your personal information as defined in S.B. 220. However, you may still submit an opt-out request, and if our practices were to change in the future, we would honor your request. If you are a Nevada resident and would like to opt out of the sale of your covered information, your request must be submitted to [support@tvtime.com](mailto:support@tvtime.com). Your request must include your full name, street address, city, state, zip code, and a valid email address so that we can contact you if needed regarding your request. If you previously provided a phone number, including it will assist us in making sure we identify you as someone who wants to opt out. You may be required to take reasonable steps as we determine from time to time to verify your identity and/or the authenticity of your request.

### 14\. Notice to California Residents \[UPDATED\]

**This California Privacy Notice is effective as of April 22, 2024.**

This Notice supplements WNI’s Privacy Policy and applies only to California residents. We adopt this Notice to conform to the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018, the California Privacy Rights Act, and any implementing regulations adopted thereunder (collectively, the “CCPA”). Any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meaning when used in this Section.

**EXERCISING YOUR CALIFORNIA RIGHTS**

California residents have the right to request: (1) that we disclose to you what Personal Information we collect, use, disclose, and sell, including the right to request that we provide to you the categories and the specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you ("Right to Know"); (2) that we delete the Personal Information we collected about you ("Right to Delete"); (3) that we correct inaccurate Personal Information we hold about you (“Right to Collect”), (4) to opt-out from the sharing of your Personal Information to a third party for cross-context behavioral advertising (i.e., targeted advertising) (“Right to Opt-Out of Sharing”), (5) to opt-out from the sale of their Personal Information (“Right to Opt-Out of Sale”), and (6) that we limit the use or disclosure of your Sensitive Personal Information (SPI) to purposes set forth under the CCPA, including what is necessary and anticipated to perform the services or provide the goods reasonably expected by an average consumer who requests those goods or services (“Right to Limit Use and Disclosure of SPI”), all subject to meanings and exceptions set forth in the CCPA. More information on how to exercise these rights is below.

Please note that our business activities do not use personal information in a manner that triggers the Right to Limit Use and Disclosure of SPI.

California residents have the right to not receive discriminatory treatment for exercising CCPA rights. We will not discriminate against you for exercising your CCPA rights.

**Verifying Your Requests**

Please note that we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity in order to fulfill your request. In order to verify your identity, we will request that you provide: your user ID, email address, and the most recent episode you marked as tracked.

In your request, you must provide enough information to allow us to verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information, or their authorized representative. You must also describe your request with enough detail so that we can understand, evaluate and respond to it. We can’t respond to your request if we can’t verify your identity. Making such a request does not require you to create an account with us, and we will only use the information you provide in a request to verify your identity. When you exercise your Right to Know, Right to Delete, and/or Right to Correct, we may ask that you provide us with information, beyond the above, in order to verify your identity and fulfill your request.

If we are unable to verify that the individual submitting the request is the same individual about whom we have collected information (or someone authorized by that individual to act on their behalf), we will not be able to process the request.

**Agents**

If you are an authorized representative submitting a request on a user’s behalf, please submit the request per the instructions below. We will follow up to request a signed, written permission signed by the individual who is the subject of the request authorizing you to make the request on their behalf. The written permission must state your full legal name, the full legal name of the individual who is the subject of the request and needs to be clear about the permission granted.

Alternatively, you may submit a copy of a power of attorney under Probate Code sections 4000-4465. In either case, please also indicate in your email the nature of your request. The consumer’s identity, in addition to your own, will need to be independently verified in order for us to be able to fulfill your request. We may also ask the consumer to directly confirm with us that they provided you permission to submit a request. Please keep in mind that if we do not receive adequate proof that you are authorized to act on the consumer’s behalf, we may deny the request.

**Submitting Your Requests**

If you are a California Consumer and would like to exercise your rights please email us at[legal@whipmedia.com](mailto:legal@whipmedia.com) or mail us your request at Whip Networks, Inc., 1841 Centinela Ave., Santa Monica, CA 90404. Your request must include your username (if you have one) and email address; please also include any additional information that you have submitted to us that may help us verify you as set forth below.

**Other Important Information**

* Requests to Know
    
    In order to have us provide specific pieces of information, we will require a signed declaration under penalty of perjury that you are the consumer whose Personal Information is the subject of the request.
    
* Requests to Delete
    
    To ensure that we do not delete your personal information in response to a fraudulent request, once you submit the request, we may follow up to confirm that you want your information to be deleted.
    
* Do Not Sell or Share for Cross-Context Behavioral Advertising
    
    The CCPA also provides California Consumers a right to request to opt-out of the sale and sharing of Personal Information (i.e., for targeted advertising). WNI does not sell Personal Information to third parties for financial gain. However, WNI does engage in online advertising practices (and certain analytics or similar activities), such as to provide you relevant marketing messages, which may potentially be considered “sales” or “sharing” under the CCPA under certain circumstances.[Click Here](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy) to manage your cookie preferences for the tvtime.com website.
    
    In addition, the Digital Advertising Alliance also offers tools for California consumers to send requests under the CCPA to opt out of the sale of personal information by some or all of the participating companies. See: https://www.privacyrights.info/.

**DO NOT TRACK**

Some browsers incorporate a 'Do Not Track' (DNT) feature that, when turned on, signals to websites and online services that you do not wish to be tracked. Because there is not yet an accepted standard for how to respond to browser DNT signals, we do not currently respond to them.

**DATA RETENTION**

We retain your Personal Information while you have an account with us and while you continue to use or visit any of the TV Time services. We will retain your Personal Information for as long as it is reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this California Notice, considering the time period reasonably necessary to: provide the TV Time services to you; exercise the choices and rights you have requested; comply with our contractual obligations; enforce our terms for use; and comply with legal and regulatory requirements, including if a longer retention period is permitted or required by law.

**USERS YOUNGER THAN 16**

We do not knowingly sell or share personal information of minors under 16 years of age.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION WNI COLLECTS**

We collect certain types of information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or device (“Personal Information”). The Personal Information we collect about you will depend on how you use TV Time or otherwise interact with us. Accordingly, we may not collect all of the below information about you.

In addition to the below, we may collect and/or use additional types of information, and will do so after providing notice to you and obtaining your consent to the extent such notice and consent is required by the CCPA.

| Category of Personal Information Collected | Business or Commercial Purpose(s) for which Information is Collected | Categories of Sources from Which Collected | Categories of Third Parties with whom Information is Shared/Disclosed for Business Purpose | Categories of Third Parties to Whom This Type of Personal Information Is Sold |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Identifiers  <br>  <br>Examples: name, email address, and device identifiers | To provide TV Time to you and allow you to participate in the features TV Time offer  <br>  <br>To help us to improve TV Time and to serve you better  <br>  <br>For legal, regulatory, administrative, and internal business purposes  <br>  <br>To protect against misuse of TV Time, fraud, or criminal activity  <br>  <br>To detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies for TV Time  <br>  <br>For other purposes described to you at the time of collection or otherwise consistent with this Privacy Policy | You  <br>  <br>Third party service providers and business partners  <br>  <br>Cookies and other tracking technologies | Other Users  <br>  <br>Service Providers  <br>  <br>Third parties whose features are integrated with TV Time, such as social media companies  <br>  <br>Third party advertising and analytics companies  <br>  <br>Third parties who may acquire your information in connection with a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition  <br>  <br>Third parties or affiliated companies when you request that we share your information with them  <br>  <br>Other third parties (including government entities) to comply with laws, regulations, or legal requests or to protect or defend our rights or the rights of any third party  <br>  <br>Third parties when you agree to or request that we share your information with them. | Third party advertising, analytics, and similar business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances. |
| B. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e))  <br>  <br>Examples: name, email address, phone number | To provide TV Time to you and allow you to participate in the features TV Time offer  <br>  <br>To help us to improve TV Time and to serve you better  <br>  <br>For legal, regulatory, administrative, and internal business purposes  <br>  <br>To protect against misuse of TV Time, fraud, or criminal activity  <br>  <br>To detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies for TV Time  <br>  <br>For other purposes described to you at the time of collection or otherwise consistent with this Privacy Policy | You  <br>  <br>Other Users  <br>  <br>Third party service providers and business partners | Other Users  <br>  <br>Service Providers  <br>  <br>Third parties whose features are integrated with TV Time, such as social media companies  <br>  <br>Third party advertising and analytics companies  <br>  <br>Third parties who may acquire your information in connection with a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition  <br>  <br>Third parties or affiliated companies when you request that we share your information with them  <br>  <br>Other third parties (including government entities) to comply with laws, regulations, or legal requests or to protect or defend our rights or the rights of any third party  <br>  <br>Third parties when you agree to or request that we share your information with them. | Third party advertising, analytics, and similar business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances |
| C. Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law  <br>  <br>Examples: gender, age, ethnicity | To provide TV Time to you and allow you to participate in the features TV Time offer  <br>  <br>To help us improve TV Time and to serve you better  <br>  <br>For legal, regulatory, administrative, and internal business purposes  <br>  <br>To protect against misuse of TV Time, fraud, or criminal activity  <br>  <br>To detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies for TV Time  <br>  <br>For other purposes described to you at the time of collection or otherwise consistent with this Privacy Policy | You  <br>  <br>Third party service providers and business partners | Other Users  <br>  <br>Service Providers  <br>  <br>Third parties whose features are integrated with TV Time, such as social media companies  <br>  <br>Third party advertising and analytics companies  <br>  <br>Third parties who may acquire your information in connection with a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition  <br>  <br>Third parties or affiliated companies when you request that we share your information with them  <br>  <br>Other third parties (including government entities) to comply with laws, regulations, or legal requests or to protect or defend our rights or the rights of any third party  <br>  <br>Third parties when you agree to or request that we share your information with them. | Not applicable |
| D. Commercial information  <br>  <br>Examples: products or services obtained or considered; purchasing or consuming history or tendency | To provide TV Time to you and allow you to participate in the features TV Time offer  <br>  <br>To help us improve TV Time and to serve you better  <br>  <br>For legal, regulatory, administrative, and internal business purposes  <br>  <br>To protect against misuse of TV Time, fraud, or criminal activity  <br>  <br>To detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies for TV Time  <br>  <br>For other purposes described to you at the time of collection or otherwise consistent with this Privacy Policy | You  <br>  <br>Third party service providers and business partners | Other Users  <br>  <br>Service Providers  <br>  <br>Third parties whose features are integrated with TV Time, such as social media companies  <br>  <br>Third party advertising and analytics companies  <br>  <br>Third parties who may acquire your information in connection with a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition  <br>  <br>Third parties or affiliated companies when you request that we share your information with them  <br>  <br>Other third parties (including government entities) to comply with laws, regulations, or legal requests or to protect or defend our rights or the rights of any third party  <br>  <br>Third parties when you agree to or request that we share your information with them. | &Third party advertising, analytics, and similar business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances; |
| F. Internet or other similar network activity  <br>  <br>Examples: login information, areas of TV Time you visit, and devices used to access TV Time | To provide TV Time to you and allow you to participate in the features TV Time offer  <br>  <br>To help us improve TV Time and to serve you better  <br>  <br>For legal, regulatory, administrative, and internal business purposes  <br>  <br>To protect against misuse of TV Time, fraud, or criminal activity  <br>  <br>To detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies for TV Time  <br>  <br>For other purposes described to you at the time of collection or otherwise consistent with this Privacy Policy | Cookies and other tracking technologies  <br>  <br>Third party service providers and business partners | Other Users  <br>  <br>Service Providers  <br>  <br>Third parties whose features are integrated with TV Time, such as social media companies  <br>  <br>Third party advertising and analytics companies  <br>  <br>Third parties who may acquire your information in connection with a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition  <br>  <br>Third parties or affiliated companies when you request that we share your information with them  <br>  <br>Other third parties (including government entities) to comply with laws, regulations, or legal requests or to protect or defend our rights or the rights of any third party  <br>  <br>Third parties when you agree to or request that we share your information with them. | Third party advertising, analytics, and similar business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances |
| H. Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information  <br>  <br>Examples: Profile pictures | To provide TV Time to you and allow you to participate in the features TV Time offer  <br>  <br>To help us improve TV Time and to serve you better  <br>  <br>For legal, regulatory, administrative, and internal business purposes  <br>  <br>To protect against misuse of TV Time, fraud, or criminal activity  <br>  <br>To detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies for TV Time  <br>  <br>For other purposes described to you at the time of collection or otherwise consistent with this Privacy Policy | You | Other Users  <br>  <br>Service Providers  <br>  <br>Third parties whose features are integrated with TV Time, such as social media companies  <br>  <br>Third party advertising and analytics companies  <br>  <br>Third parties who may acquire your information in connection with a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition  <br>  <br>Third parties or affiliated companies when you request that we share your information with them  <br>  <br>Other third parties (including government entities) to comply with laws, regulations, or legal requests or to protect or defend our rights or the rights of any third party  <br>  <br>Third parties when you agree to or request that we share your information with them. | Not applicable |
| K. Inferences drawn from other personal information  <br>  <br>Examples: Preferences, characteristics, predispositions, behaviors | To provide TV Time to you and allow you to participate in the features TV Time offer  <br>  <br>To help us improve TV Time and to serve you better  <br>  <br>For legal, regulatory, administrative, and internal business purposes  <br>  <br>To protect against misuse of TV Time, fraud, or criminal activity  <br>  <br>To detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies for TV Time  <br>  <br>For other purposes described to you at the time of collection or otherwise consistent with this Privacy Policy | You  <br>  <br>Third party service providers  <br>  <br>Cookies and tracking technologies  <br>  <br>Third party social media companies  <br>  <br>Third party business partners such as data analytics providers, data brokers, advertising networks, or joint marketing partners | Other Users  <br>  <br>Service Providers  <br>  <br>Third parties whose features are integrated with TV Time, such as social media companies  <br>  <br>Third party advertising and analytics companies  <br>  <br>Third parties who may acquire your information in connection with a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition  <br>  <br>Third parties or affiliated companies when you request that we share your information with them  <br>  <br>Other third parties (including government entities) to comply with laws, regulations, or legal requests or to protect or defend our rights or the rights of any third party  <br>  <br>Third parties when you agree to or request that we share your information with them. | Third party advertising, analytics, and similar business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances |

**CONTACT FOR MORE INFORMATION**

Please contact us with questions or to request an alternative format of this California Notice: email us at[support@tvtime.com](mailto:support@tvtime.com) or mail us your request at Whip Networks, Inc., 1841 Centinela Ave., Santa Monica, CA 90404.

**Other California Rights**

California residents have the right to request from companies conducting business in California certain information relating to third parties to which the company has disclosed certain categories of personal information during the preceding year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that a company may comply, as WNI does, by disclosing in its privacy policy that it provides consumers choice (opt-out or opt-in) regarding sharing personal information with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes, and information on how to exercise that choice. WNI will provide you choice prior to sharing your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you do not opt-in or if you choose to opt-out at the time WNI offers that choice, we will not share your personal information with that third party for its direct marketing purposes.

California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by e-mailing [support@tvtime.com](mailto:support@tvtime.com) or writing to us at Whip Networks, Inc., 1841 Centinela Ave., Santa Monica, CA 90404. You must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the subject field of your email or in the address line of your envelope. You must include your name, street address, city, state, and ZIP code. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.

### 15\. Information for European Union/European Economic Area, and United Kingdom Residents

**Legal Basis for Processing**

We will only collect, store, or otherwise process Personal Information collected from you in the EU/EEA or the UK in the following situations:

* When we have your consent to do so. For example, if you opt in to receive promotional emails. You can withdraw your consent at any time as described below or directly through the Services.
    
* When we need to use your Personal Data to perform our responsibilities under our contract with you (e.g. providing the Services you have requested).
    
* When we or a third party have a legitimate interest in processing your Personal Data. For example, we may process your Personal Data to communicate with you about our Services, to provide, secure, and improve our Services, and, in certain circumstances, to deliver advertising to you. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data that is based on our legitimate interests.
    
* When we are required by law to process the Personal Data.

**EU/EEA and UK Data Subject Rights**

The GDPR (EU General Data Protection Regulation) provides certain rights for EU/EEA residents. Residents of the United Kingdom have similar rights under the UK GDPR and Data Privacy Act. You can access information about you and update or correct it. In some cases, you can also ask us to erase it, restrict or stop processing, or provide data in a “portable” form, if feasible. You may withdraw consent (“opt-out”) if you have previously consented to any particular use of your information, such as receiving emails or text messages. For all requests, contact [support@tvtime.com](mailto:support@tvtime.com). You may also decline to share certain Personal Data with us, in which case we may not be able to provide some or all of the features and functionality of our TV Time services.

You may make some changes to your information via your profile or settings sections, as described in the “**[Your Choices About the Information We Collect](https://www.tvtime.com/privacy/#toc_6)**” section, above.

We will reply to your data subject requests within 30 days. We will verify your identity and/or requests as described in the Notice to California Residents section above. If we cannot fulfill your request within 30 days, we will inform you when we will be able to do so. We will also provide an explanation if we do not fully comply with your request. When technically feasible, at your request, we will provide your Personal Data to you or transmit it directly to another controller.

**Retention of Information**

We retain your Personal Data while you have an account with us and while you continue to use or visit any of the TV Time services. We will retain your Personal Data for as long as it is reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, considering the time period reasonably necessary to: provide the TV Time services to you; exercise the choices and rights you have requested; comply with our contractual obligations; enforce our terms for use; and comply with legal and regulatory requirements.

**Inquiries and Complaints**

Please first contact us as set forth below. EU/EEA and UK residents have the right to make a complaint to your national data protection supervisory authority if you do not believe we have resolved your concern.

**Contact Us**

For all EU/EEA and UK Data Subject Rights requests, please put the statement "Your EU/UK Data Subject Rights" in the subject field of your request. Please provide your contact information in your request and clearly indicate that you are requesting information with respect to our TV Time services.

Email: [support@tvtime.com](mailto:support@tvtime.com)

Address:  
Mediamorph Europe Limited (UK Domestic Representative)  
132a Webber Street  
Southwark, London SE1 0QL

or

Mediamorph, BV (EU/EEA Domestic Representative)  
Hoogoorddreef 15, 1101 BA  
Amsterdam, the Netherlands  

European/UK residents also may learn more about interest-based advertisements from participating third parties at the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance page at [www.youronlinechoices.eu](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

### 16\. Additional Information for Canadian Residents

We make reasonable efforts to notify you of the purposes for which personal information will be used or disclosed and if the initial purpose changes. Please note, you may withdraw consent at any time (subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice). Subject to certain limits set out in the applicable laws, Canadian residents also have the right to request access to the personal information that WNI collects and to update or correct personal information if it is inaccurate.

If you are a Canadian resident and would like to submit a request to access your personal information or to withdraw consent to the processing of your personal data, you must submit your request by sending an email to [support@tvtime.com](mailto:support@tvtime.com). You may also use this contact to submit any requests for information on WNI’s privacy practices or to submit a complaint regarding our practices.

Your request or complaint must include your full name, street address, city, province, postal code, and an email address so that we are able to contact you if needed regarding this request.

We cannot properly process requests or complaints that do not come through the designated request mechanism or do not contain sufficient information to allow us to process your request. You may also be required to take reasonable steps as we determine from time to time in order to verify your identity and/or the authenticity of the request. Once your request is processed, absent exemptions, we will provide you with details regarding what personal information we have, how it is used, and with which third parties it is shared.

Canadian residents may have additional rights under Canadian law, including the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) and successor legislation. Please see the website of the Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada ([www.priv.gc.ca](http://www.priv.gc.ca/)) for further information.

Canadian residents also may learn more about interest-based advertisements from participating third parties in Canada at the Canadian DAA choice page at [https://youradchoices.ca/choices](https://youradchoices.ca/en/tools).

You and We confirm that it is our wish that this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use, and all other related policies be drawn up in English.

### 17\. Additional Information if You Are Located in Countries Outside the US, EU/EEA, UK, or Canada

In certain jurisdictions with relevant data protection laws, including (without limitation) Argentina, Australia, Brazil, Canada, China, Hong Kong, India, Japan, Malaysia, Mexico, Philippines, Singapore, South Africa, Switzerland, and Taiwan, we may require your consent or authorization to use or share your Personal Data for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. By providing your Personal Data to us, you expressly provide such consent or authorization to the extent it is required.

In addition, you may have additional privacy rights under the law of your country of residence, typically including the rights to access, correct, delete, or object to further processing of your Personal Data. We handle requests to exercise such rights similarly to requests from EU residents under the EU GDPR, as described above.
